Here's something I haven't done in a long, long time. A text thread.
This puppy is something Matt sent me this morning and it's special. It is irresistible. I have to
app about it. A guy had been seeing a girly match with on Hinge for like two weeks. They'd only hung out
a couple of times. But he wasn't really enjoying her company all that much. And instead of just
ghosting her and disappearing, decided to just rip the bandaid off and put in his two weeks notice.
You know, like I'm resigning from this, we had some good times, but you know, we need to go our
separate ways into the sunset here. And all hell broke loose. It was a pretty respectable message.
Hey, I'm realizing we're not aligned in ways that matter to me. I'd rather be honest now than
keep moving forward when I don't see it working out long term. Very concise to the point. It's not
rude. Very simple. And man, that hit like the meteor to the dinosaurs here. Oh, well, okay.
I hope you find what you're looking for, I guess. Me thinking I found my person and you don't even
feel the same. LMAO. You just says same to you. Now I'm sad. Block me. All because I want to tell you
conspiracies and I want kids. Now you know me. I love conspiracies like Garfield loves lasagna. But
there comes a point where it's just overwhelming. This individual here, she's not just wanting to tell
him conspiracies. She is obsessed with conspiracies. She lives in breeds. In conspiracies out the
wazoo. You're about to see just like a flood of unhinged like Lord dumping. She starts trying to
give this guy a homework on conspiracies. She then gets into anime monologue territory. It's also
been five days and people change. Life changes. Circumstances change. But war, war never changes. And
you know what else doesn't change? Once you reach a certain age, that is your height. Doesn't that damn
I actually felt something with you which isn't something that happens often. But you know what?
You want from your person, I guess. I don't know why I'm reading this like AI. It's first thing in
the morning. Now we can actually fight. Thank God. It's about time. We can actually fight. Woo! Yeah.
What a weird thing to throw in there. That's what I get for liking a lib. I'm upset because what the
fuck fix your feelings. I don't care. Men and their illusion of options. Yes, you see there's only
one option and it's her. All roads lead back to this angel. I told you at dinner, I like to talk
out my ass when it comes to conspiracies. I thought I fell in love with you when I came over in the
entire time. You didn't even want me there. That's delusion and that's okay. God. That's like just
scary. The fixation like how quickly that can happen. I thought I fell in love with you when they
only hung out like a handful of times over the course of two weeks. Thank you for your time,
Elameo. I am again done dating for a few months. Our weak pictures. I can't quite make out what
that's supposed to be. It looks like the inside of a dishwasher. I don't know if they shrunk themselves
down on Miss Frizzle's school buzz or something and took an adventure inside of a dishwasher. But
that's what it looks like to me. I'm not really sure. But she sends like some pictures to commemorate
the great times they had together. Now I have to take down and restart my hair because why am I
literally doing it pink like you wanted? I have to kill you on Sims. That's one of those big red flags
right there. There's a lot to unpack with just that one line. Now I have to kill you on Sims. That's
that psychoshit like ripping the wings off a butterfly. First of all, she made him in Sims. After
I guess she was like planning their lives together through Sims to see if it's something that she
you know is ready to you know get ripping and roaring on. And now that it's gone south, she's
going to have to execute and murder him on the Sims. I imagine there will be torture involved too.
Just a hunch. Just a hunch. A girl that actually likes you is too much Elameo. Anyways, I'll see you
Saturday. I love that after all this. It's like okay, so now that you're done being stupid
about this whole like we don't align type of thing. I'm going to see you on Saturday, isn't that right?
I will see you Saturday. Don't you forget it. I will see you Saturday. Yes, I killed you on the Sims,
but I had to do what I had to do. It doesn't mean I don't want to see you on Saturday. We're still
so much. We're meant to be together. You know that. I like you. You know that. And you don't have a
choice. It's an illusion of options. First day you didn't see me in a row and I got my man taken.
I mean, man didn't get taken. Man just came to his senses. This is all very concerning stuff.
It's like it is what it is. He was up front with you about it. He didn't ghost you. And man,
I got to tell you, I think overall this response to it is showing that maybe this just wasn't the right fit.
Telling me to keep you just for you to leave. I'm sorry for blowing you up, but I'm just a
deeply loyal person. I don't see what we don't agree on. And even when, and even then, why do we
have to agree on everything? We're human with our own lifestyles and experiences. I'm so sad.
While I'm sensitive and bleeding isn't nice, could have waited two days when I'm back to being
myself. And then she puts a screenshot from another match she had on hinge, where she's talking
about the Mossad and the CIA, which I'm not really sure what that has to do with what's going on
here, but she does provide it regardless. I guess as like some parting ways reading to brush up
if you want the real. This is why I hate liberal men because why are you more sensitive than me?
Well, I think him sending one message about like, hey, it's not working out. I don't really love
us together. And then you having 45 messages over the course of like an hour and a half.
It doesn't seem like he's more sensitive at all. Actually, that's kind of a weird projection,
to be honest. That's a bit of a reach. I'll give you one more, I'll give you one day of space.
I'll see you tomorrow, caps locked. She's going to be in like a fucking tree with binoculars looking
at him, spying or something, smiley face. Yeah, I don't care. You're either with me or we're
together. Those are your only two options. Oh, fuck. About the kidnap them or something. It reminds me
of that hat. You're either drinking 14 beers with me or you're drinking 14 beers against me.
Your cute smart laugh at all my jokes. Easy to talk to. I like your hands and your arms
and your weird nerdiness. Okay, I have shit to do, but still count your days. Literally one, but yeah.
Okay, bye. Have a good day. And then she drops some more screenshots here. This one's about
Jewish tradition and Jewish banking. So it's becoming a full blown Twitter thread here. And it
starts sending these all of this over the course of two minutes. So it's all saved to her phone.
And I'm actually so fucking hilarious. And I wanted to cook for you and love you forever.
Blocking your blessings. And I gave a maculid head.
Shit, wait, wait a minute. Hold on, hold on. He may have been too hasty here. That ought to make him
rethink everything. We can now disregard the previous 66 messages that have come through here.
And maybe we can at least reevaluate this relationship. That's quite the Hail Mary.
And I'm a trust fund kid with VA benefits because both my parents are retired and on 100%
disability. Law, okay, I'm done now. Your loss for sure. What? Internation? What kind of? What?
I don't even know what to say about that section there. I have fun with bitches that don't like you
and that aren't funny or pretty or won't want to do anything for you. I was OTP with my best friend.
I don't know what OTP stands for in League of Legends. That's one trick pony, but that doesn't really
fit here. But whatever. I was OTP with my best friend literally telling her how much I liked you
when you sent that message because what the fuck? But I know we're never going to see each other again.
So it's all a good friend. I hope your date does. I hope your date goes well. Actually, I hope she's ugly.
And loves the white savior complex. I can't feelings way too fast. My fault for sure. I'm glad you
feel safe. That's good. You could have warned me. Literally if you haven't blocked me, I don't know.
I'm gonna keep going until I feel better. I don't need to respond to anything. I feel really
defeated. But it could really just be me on my period. I was so ready to lock in. Actually, I did.
See, this is why you always have multiple men. But I didn't want multiple. I wanted one.
I want to be a stay-at-home mom in the woods with a garden in my bakery.
But you don't have just one man. You just sent a screenshot like 10 minutes ago of you talking to
another guy on Hinge about Masad. Like, what do you mean? You definitely are talking to multiple men.
But I guess this was her favorite. You want to live in the city with no kids and be 50-50 with
whomever. So I get that. But the last bitch you were with, you tricked, you tricked for. And I
didn't even want that. What does that mean? You tricked for. I'm not familiar. Like, what do you do?
Hit it like a kickflip or something to impress her? I'm not positive. But like, even she's
confirming that they want like different things. Like, it should be like a really amicable split here.
And I'm calling it a split, but they're not dating. They hardly know each other. They're just like
a step above strangers. Didn't even give you anything. Or maybe you lied. I wanted a partnership.
And you want, I don't even know actually. It's okay. I'm too pretty to be doing this. Have a good
day, especially when we have everything in common. Do you have any friends that like Mario and being in
love? Mario's like one of the most well-known property of all time. I bet he has tons of friends
like Mario. And as far as being in love goes, it's like a basic human desire that 99% of the world
also feels and wants. So yeah, I would say, I don't know this guy, but I would say with high
confidence, he probably has a lot of friends that like Mario and being in love, just a hunch.
And like obsessive conspiracy theorists. Yeah, see like conspiracy theory and yapping about it's
like really entertaining and enjoyable. But when it becomes a full-blown obsession, where it's like
all you think about and all you talk about, it's no longer fun anymore. So like that's not a good
thing. That's a negative. I do need a response actually. You haven't blocked me. Why are you letting
me still text you? Close the door and move forward with someone mediocre. That's more your speed.
I'm just gonna say you have a shrimp dick and move on. I feel better now. Well, that's good.
I'm happy to hear that. I'm glad they were both able to reach a point where they feel better
about all of this. And then she comes back a few hours later. Hey, I just wanted to apologize.
I'm not used to meeting Goodman, so I thought it was too good to be true, so I tried to scare you off.
I realize I messed up and if it's okay with you, I want another chance, even if we're just cool for
now. If not, it's okay too. You're an amazing man, honestly. I know that's quite a cliffhanger to
be left on, but according to the guy who posted this, he didn't end up blocking her after that
apology. So it's seeming like they're not going to be seeing too much of each other anymore.
Probably for the best, they don't seem super compatible. I am sure she will find someone that she
can spit conspiracy theories back and forth on. Now is the perfect day in age for that. She could
probably find 10,000 men through Twitter right now that would absolutely love her. This just wasn't,
you know, the right choice here. They weren't meant for each other and that's okay. I don't think
you need over 100 messages when A, you don't even know the person very well. You've only seen
them like a couple of times and B, it's just not that deep. It's just, it's seriously just not that deep.
Anyway, though, that's really about it. See ya.